

### CONTACT

- +86 130 1386 8592
- kalvinson910210@gmail.com
- Shenyang Huanggu District,
   Liaoning, China
- Enter Birth Date

#### **GITHUB**



Click On Icon

https://github.com/KalvinSon

### **SKILLS**

React

Vue

**Angular** 

Node.js

PHP

Laravel

HTML5 / CSS3 / JavaScript

BlockChain

# **Kalvin Son**

**Profession** 



### SUMMARY

A PROBLEM SOLVER and TECHNOLOGY ENTHUSIAST is how I can be

described the best. With almost 5 years of experience in Blockchain Domain &

more than 10 years of experience in Web,I have worked with various of the

use-cases in it and have delivered a number of enterprise grade products.

Having an unconventional career graph, I believe that 'SkillSet' and 'Talent'

should always be the key factors to look for in an individual. I have played a key role in turning startup companies into bigger ones and

have had successful track records in a fast growing startup environment.



### **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Blockchain developer

#### Webisoft Technologie inc

**iii** 2021.08~2022.07 **●** 460 S

 460 Saint-Catherine St W #305, Montreal, QC H3B 1A6, Canada

Build Fast Swap token

- Develop token contract with complex distribution (token minted via call function and time lock)
- Develop a launchpad involving allocation distribution
- · Develop a staking platform
- Develop swap exchange (fork and twist) and liquidity mining pool Develop dashboard linked all platform information

# Blockchain developer / Senior Web Developer Chimpare Designs Limited

**ii** 2018.02~2021.06

- Solent Business Park, 4500 Parkway, Whiteley, Fareham P015 7AZ, UK
- Technical assistance and consultation at the idea initiation stage
- Smart contract development and deployment for getting Raptor token out
- Development of Cryptocurrency system with Raptor Token and Wallet
- Developed some modules of Gosama platform such as customer loyalty system using MEAN stack

# Senior Full Stack Engineer ( MEAN & MERN ) **Deligence Technologies PVT. LTD**

- 106-107, First floor, Jyoti Shikar Tower, District Center, Janakpuri, New Delhi, 110058, India
- React/ React hook / Material UI front-end web application for real estate tax calculation
- Collaborate with the Ruby, TypeScript, Vue and React stack
- Closely collaborate with the lead team designer to implement new features in the design system
- Streamline Webforms' UI documentation in isolation for Storybook
- Update Storybook styled components for isolated documentation Fix and update UI's bugs in Webforms

Powered by: 🗟



### **SKILLS**

Mobile App

SOL

NonSQL

**DevOps** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

**English** 





### **EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Front-End Engineer (AngularJS)

Zenesys Technosys Pvt. Ltd

- Angular/rxjs/ angular-material web app for managing user registration for seminar and webinars hosting in firebase
- Node.js backend firebase cloud function with firestore as database and google storage as file storage
- Took 100% responsibility of the project of planning, architecting, developing and deploying

# Front-End Development Engineer (Vue.js) Long View Systems

iii 2011.10~2014.01 
■ 2 Lansing Square, Suite 200 Toronto, Ontario, Canada

- Built several vue.js web applications for VR products
- Used different UI frameworks like Ant design or Vuetify based on project design type
- Integrated headless CSM, Butter CMS for pulling data and assets



### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

**University of British Columbia, BC** 

- Obtained First Class with Distinction in all the semesters
- Earned the accolade, "Best Outgoing Student Academics" for the year 2013

Powered by: 🗟 🗘